(Howard:)Most engineers
don't bother with a PhD.
(Howard:)But you may be
interested to know
(Howard:)I designed the zero-gravity
waste-disposal system for NASA.
(Mrs Latham:)Got it--
you're a space plumber.
(Howard:)I'm gonna go hit the bar.
(Mrs Latham:)Tell me about
these two.
- Do him first.
- Dr. Hofstadter
(Seibert:)is representing our
experimental physics
program tonight.
(Seibert:)I think you'll
really enjoy
(Seibert:)hearing about his
fascinating work.
(Seibert:)Right.
(Mrs Latham:)Fascinate me.
(Mrs Latham:)They're cute when they're about
to wet themselves, aren't they?
(Mrs Latham:)I'll make it
easy for you.
(Mrs Latham:)When you arrive at the lab
in the morning,
(Mrs Latham:)what sort of machine
do you turn on?
(Leonard:)Coffee maker?
(Mrs Latham:)All right, Dr. Kooth--
uh, whatever it is-- you're up.
(Raj:)It's Koothrappali.
(Raj:)I have to tinkle.
(Sheldon:)And so, instead
of bowing to pressure,
(Sheldon:)and going to that
pointless soiree,
(Sheldon:)I stayed right here
and did a load of whites.